//This function PUT to the API new data
async function saveProductAPI(title, price, description,
image, featured, form, formTitle) {





+47 93859246

pkderlam@hotmail.com

Trondheim – Norway

Profile

I am punctual and tidy. I am honest, responsible, efficient, reliable and trustworthy.

I have a good mood and a positive service attitude. I want to learn new skills and acquire work experience.

Skills

5 HTML	React	Ps	Photoshop

Languages

Portuguese - Native

English - B1

Norwegian - A2

Spanish - A1

Volunteer Work

Volunteer in COVID-19 vaccination in Trondheim – Jun, 2021 - Aug, 2021 / Dec, 2021 – Feb, 2022

Academic Background

Vocational Degree – Front-end Developer Noroff – Norway – (2020 – 2022)

Bachelor Degree – Law
<u>UCS</u> – Brazil – (2013 – 2018)

Licentiate Degree – Portuguese and Brazilian Literature UFRGS – Brazil – (2008 – 2012)

Vocational Degree – Software System Development <u>CETEC UCS</u> – Brazil – (2002 – 2006)

Professional Experience

Police Officer (Dec 2014 – Aug 2020) at Polícia Civil do Rio Grande do Sul/Brazil

Portuguese Teacher (Feb 2014 – Jun 2014) at EMEF João de Zorzi at Caxias do Sul/Brazil

Portuguese Teacher (2012-2013) at EMEF Aracy Gomes Valim at Arroio do Sal/ Brazil

Technical Assistant (Jun 2007 – Feb 2008) at MI Comércio e Servicos de Informática at Caxias do Sul/Brazil.

Projects



```
.message__form");
     } catch (error) {
        console.log(error);
        displayMessage("error", error,
.message__form");
    }
```